Kevin Doh

San Jose, CA 95138

Phone: 408-960-5481 | Email: <u>kdoh52@gmail.com</u>

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/kdoh/ | GitHub: https://github.com/kdoh52

Portfolio: https://kdoh52.github.io/

Summary

Full Stack Web Developer employing UI/UX design experience to build efficient and intuitive web applications. Effectively combines technical and creative skills to develop solutions both visual and practical. Thrives in a collaborative environment using detailed communication and attentiveness of outside perspectives.

Technical Skills

Languages: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Express, SQL, Handlebars, Python

Frameworks/Libraries: Node.js, React, MongoDB, Mongoose, APIs, jQuery, AJAX, JSON, Bootstrap,

Material-UI

Applications: Visual Studio Code, GitHub, MySQL, Adobe Creative Suite

Projects

The Coder's Corner | Repository: https://the-coders-corner | Application: https://the-coders-corner.herokuapp.com/

- Social media website geared towards helping web developers network, learn, and collaborate.
- Implemented newsfeed and chat pages. Assisted in user authentication, back-end routing, APIs, database management, and general debugging
- HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Node.js, Axios, Bcryptjs, Express, MongoDB, Mongoose, Passport, Socket.io, Validator, React, React-Router-Dom, Material-UI, Heroku

Google Books Search | Repository: https://afternoon-hamlet-63363.herokuapp.com/

- Website that allows a user to search the Google Books API and save/remove books from their collection
- Implemented search bar to query the API and display results using react components.

 Connected MongoDB database to allow for book information to be stored in a separate tab.
- HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Node.js, Express, MongoDB, Mongoose, Axios, React, React-Router-Dom, Material-UI, Heroku

Fitness Tracker | Repository: https://github.com/kdoh52/hw-17 | Application: https://lit-taiga-57650.herokuapp.com/

- Fitness tracker that allows a user to save workouts and view their progress graphically
- Connected front-end application to MongoDB database for inputting workouts and retrieving past data.
- HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Node.js, Express, Compression, MongoDB, Mongoose, Morgan, Bootstrap, Chart.js, Heroku

Experience

Student Graphic Designer (Oct 2019 - Aug 2020)

UC Davis Global Affairs — Davis, CA

Designed and edited graphics for promotional materials including posters, web pages, flyers, etc. Created visual solutions given constraints and specifications from project coordinators. Collaborated with others on a regular basis.

Social Media / Design Intern (Apr 2019 - Sep 2019)

Davis Sensory Institute — Davis, CA

Redesigned and maintained company website. Designed graphics for various publications. Assisted in conducting sensory research.

Artistic Advisor (Oct 2018 - May 2019)

SoNE1 — Davis, CA

Co-managed team practices. Collaborated with members in developing pieces. Designed graphics for social media. Mixed audio and edited videos for YouTube channel with over 250,000 subscribers.

Education

Coding Bootcamp Certification: Full Stack Web Development University of California, Davis Jun 2020 - Dec 2020

Bachelor of Arts (BA): UI/UX Design University of California, Davis Sept 2017 - Dec 2020